question_data = [
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the current president of Nigeria? \n 1. Ahmed Musa \n 2. Piter Gregory Obi "
                    "\n 3. Muhammadu Buhari \n 4. Donald Trump \n",
        'answer': 3,
    },
    {
        'question': "Which is the capital of Nigeria? \n 1. Abuja \n 2. Ado-Ekiti \n 3. Imo \n 4. Ibadan \n",
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': "When did Nigeria become independent? \n 1. 2002 \n 2. 1960 "
                    "\n 3. 1778 \n 4. 1990 \n",
        'answer': 2
    },
    {
        'question': "Which is the official language of Nigeria? \n 1. English \n 2. Yoruba "
                    "\n 3. French \n 4. Spanish \n",
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': "When is National Day Nigeria? \n 1. 11 May \n 2. January 27"
                    "\n 3. December 25 \n 4. October 1 \n",
        'answer': 4,
    },
    {
        'question': "What is the currency of Nigeria? \n 1. Dollar \n 2. Naira \n 3. Pound \n 4. Cedis \n",
        'answer': 2
    },
    {
        'question': "Which Country won the last Worldcup? \n 1. Argentina \n 2. France \n 3. India \n 4. Nigeria \n",
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': "What does the white color on the nigerian flag mean? \n 1. Conflict \n 2. Love"
                    " \n 3. Peace \n 4. War \n",
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': "How many Local governments do we have in Nigeria? \n 1. 419 \n 2. 200 "
                    "\n 3. 198 \n 4. 774 \n",
        'answer': 4
    },
    {
        'question': "Which was the first president of Nigeria? \n 1. Odumodublvck \n 2. Dr. Tony Elumelu "
                    "\n 3. Dr Nnamdi Azikiwe \n 4. Obafemi Awolowo \n",
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': "How many states do we have in Nigeria? \n 1. 36 \n 2. 47 \n 3. 22 \n 4. 34 \n",
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': "Which Country won the last AFCON? \n 1. Ghana \n 2. Nigeria \n 3. Senegal \n 4. Egypt \n",
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': "Which is the largest city in Nigeria? \n 1. Imo \n 2. Calabar \n 3. Lagos \n 4. Kogi \n",
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': "Who is the longest serving senate President of Nigeria? \n 1. David Mark \n 2. Nnamdi Azikiwe "
                    "\n 3. Piter Obi \n 4. Afe Babalola \n",
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': "How long does it take the earth to complete one revolution? \n 1. 365 Days \n 2. 442 Days "
                    "\n 3. 360 Days \n 4. 230 Days \n",
        'answer': 1
    }
]
